

# ANNA NACZKE JUNOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Programming fascinates me because of its logic and endless possibilities. Having completed an intensive Frontend Developer course in SDA, I'm continue self-learning to improve my skills. I also studied UX/ UI research and design as I am interested in web graphics styles. Learning new things gives me great satisfaction.

In my marketing career, I have been responsible for a great number of marketing projects, including new website design, rebranding, visual identification, promotional movies, product info materials, international fairs. I have considerable experience in designing videos and static graphics for social media as I administrated company profiles on LinkedIn, Facebook, Instagram and YouTube. With a long record of creating content for websites, marketing materials and newsletters both in Polish and English I have proved my copywriting skills.

# MY CONTACT DATA

anna.naczke@gmail.com

+48 696 333 214

in linkedin.com/in/anna-naczke/

https://github.com/anaczke

Gdańsk

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- TypeScript
- GIT
- HTTP
- JavaScript API
- Firebase
- Jest
- Figma

# MARKETING/ SOCIAL MEDIA

Social media [mo] [Fe] |
Website management - WordPress
Canva - design & video editing |
Content creation | Fairs exhibiting |
Photopea | Project Management |
Marketing Strategy

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Passionate about learning new things Determined in searching for solutions Open to new ideas | Reliable team player

# LANGUAGES

English C1 Polish native

# HOBBIES & INTERESTS

I am a ceramic artist. I run a small ceramic studio.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Frontend Developer**

Software Development Academy | 04-07/2022 | 240h course

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | Redux | TypeScript | GIT | HTTP | JavaScript - API | Firebase | Jest

#### Social Media Manager

WSAiB in Gdynia & Beeffective Agency | 2021 - 2022 | 180h postgraduate studies

Brand strategy in SM | Google Analytics and Tag Manager | Legal aspects of SM | Social Commerce | Video Marketing | Marketing Automation | Employer Barnading | Influencer Marketing | SM Paid Campaigns

## **UX Designer**

InfoShare Academy | 09-11/2019 | 45h course

UX Research | User oriented design | Prototyping in Figma | Psychological and business aspects of UX design

# **English Philology**

University of Gdansk | 2009 - 2011 | second-cycle academic studies | Master's degree

#### **Public Relations**

Wyzsza Szkola Bankowa in Poznan | Postgraduate studies

# **Economic studies**

Leicester University, UK | one semester Tempus scholarship

## **Economics with major in Marketing**

University of Gdansk | five years academic studies | Master's degree

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

complete list available on my LinkedIn account

# Social Media & Online Marketing Manager

HEXONIC | 2021-2022

- Building a strong company brand on the Social Media LinkedIn, Instagram, Facebook, YT
- New website hexonic.com creation and content management
- Google Analytics, Google Ads

## **Marketing Manager**

SECESPOL/HEXONIC | 2012-2021

- Rebranding of the company new name Hexonic and CI
- Promotional and professional texts, internal newsletter, and social media both in PL and EN
- International fairs, esp. in Frankfurt, Moscow, Kyiv, USA
- Promotional materials in several languages (movies, catalogs, presentations, documentation)
- Managing a small team